Thomas Barenghi

Full Stack Developer

Haedo, Buenos Aires - Argentina

■ linkedin.com/in/thomasbarenghi
■ github.com/thomasbarenghi
⊕ thomasbarenghi.com
⋈ thomasbarenghi@gmail.com
■ +54 11 6996-1733

Professional profile

My career in the technology field began at the age of 12 and since then, I have been involved in projects related to IoT and web development. I have had the privilege of leading and collaborating in both national and international teams, working with more than 120 people. During these experiences, I have focused my efforts on the development of soft skills and the application of agile methodologies.

Experience

Full Stack Developer & Team Leader

Jun. 2023 - Present

NoCountry | Volunteering - Ad Honorem Work

I play the role of fullstack developer, I am also Team Leader of two or three other teams. I have worked with more than 120 people in the last few months.

- I organize team tasks and responsibilities. I implement scalable solutions in development.
- I contribute to fluid and effective communication with the development and UX/UI teams.
- I establish follow-up meetings, I guarantee efficient communication.
- I complete the team control, assistance and progress form.

Technical specialist Oct. 2021 - Dec. 2022

Cibeles Service

For a year, I played the role of Technical Specialist at Cibeles Service, an appliance repair company in the province of Buenos Aires.

- Ability to work autonomously and assume responsibility for assigned projects.
- Efficiency in time management and compliance with established deadlines.
- Ability to adapt to dynamic and rapidly changing work environments.

Lidar Image and Video Analyst for Al

May. 2021 - Sep. 2021

Smart Ecosystem Philippines Inc.

I participated in an InHouse program, in which I gained knowledge about reading spectrograms, segmentation on frames and analysis of LiDAR sensors in 2D/3D fields.

- Ability to effectively communicate findings and conclusions derived from data analysis.
- Ability to identify patterns, trends and anomalies in data.
- Ability to quickly adapt to team dynamics and assigned roles.

Projects

Spaces | No Country Jul. 2023 - Ago. 2023

NoCountry - Ad honorem

Spaces is a Trello-like app that allows users to collaborate on organizing projects, tasks, and activities in a shared environment. Users can create spaces, within which they can create rooms and assign tasks to these rooms. Each space can have multiple members with different roles.

Front: NextJS, Redux Toolkit, Sass, TailwindCSS, Typescript

Back: Springboot, GraphQL **Database:** MongoDB

https://github.com/thomasbarenghi/spaces-app

BeatConnect | Soy Henry

Abr. 2023 - May. 2023

Academic experience. Henry Bootcamp

As a member of a team of eight colleagues, I had the opportunity to contribute to the development of BeatConnect, an instrumental marketplace. I was responsible for the complete development of Redux, focusing on modularization and following good development practices. Additionally, I designed the user interface and was responsible for developing most of the frontend.

Front: NextJS, Redux Toolkit, Sass, TailwindCSS

Back: ExpressJS, OAuth, Firestore **Database:** MongoDB y Mongoose.

aithub.com/thomasbarenghi/PF-Beat Connect

Technologies

- Frontend: Html, Css, Sass, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Jquery, Javascript, React, NextJS, Redux/RTK, SocketlO, PeerJS, Typescript, GraphQL.
- Backend: NodeJS, Express, Springboot, NestJS, SocketlO, PeerJS, Java.
- Databases: MongoDB, SQLite, PostgreSQL.
- Others: Postman, Firestore, FTP (Filezilla), Hosting, Xampp, SEO, Arduino, C, Blynk, Wordpress, Elementor, Crocoblock, Figma.
- Office systems: Excel (Basic), Word (Intermediate).

Professional education

- Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 700 hours of theoretical-practical courses. May 2023.
- Electronics Technician. E.E.S.T No. 8 of Morón. December 2021.

Courses and certifications

- English Certificate B1 Intermediate. EFSET. May 2023.
- CSS Skills Certification Test. HackerRank. July 2023.
- Agile Methodologies, Scrum & User Stories. Henry. May 2023.
- Quality management. National University of La Matanza. 2021.
- Product development. National University of La Matanza. 2021.